like said welcome brothers and sisters
to another Wednesday question and answer
will we open up with the Ten
Commandments that God had written for
the whole world to keep brother James
yes sir and God spake all these words
saying I am the Lord thy God which have
brought thee out of the land of Egypt
out of the house of bondage Thou shalt
have no other gods before me Thou shalt
not make unto thee any Graven image or
any likeness of anything that is in
heaven above o or that is in the earth
beneath or that is in the water under
the Earth Thou shalt not bow down
thyself to them nor serve them for I the
Lord thy God am a jealous God visiting
the iniquity of the fathers upon the
children unto the third and fourth
generation of them that hate me and
showing Mercy unto thousands of them
that love me and keep my Commandments
Thou shalt not take the name of the Lord
thy God in vain for the Lord will not
hold him Guiltless that taketh his name
in vain remember the Sabbath day to keep
it holy six days shalt thou labor and do
all thy work but the seventh day is the
Sabbath of the Lord thy God in it Thou
shalt not do any work thou nor thy son
nor thy daughter thy manservant nor thy
maid servant nor thy cattle nor thy
stranger that is within thy gates for in
six days the Lord made heaven and Earth
the sea and all that in them is and
resteth the seventh day wherefore the
Lord blessed the Sabbath day and HED it
honor thy father and thy mother that thy
days may be long upon the land which the
Lord thy God giveth thee Thou shalt not
kill Thou shalt not commit adultery Thou
shalt not steal Thou shalt not bear
false witness against thy neighbor Thou
shalt not covet thy neighbor's house
Thou shalt not covet Thy Neighbor 's
wife nor his man's servant nor his maid
servant nor his Ox nor his ass nor
anything that is thy neighbors I read
Exodus 20:
1-17 may the Lord add a blessing to the
reading of his word in Jesus name we
pray amen
amen so here on question and answer you
can ask us a question and we'll answered
according to the King James Bible and if
we cannot find the answer we will seek
further counsel to bring you answer at a
later time keep in mind that all vague
questions will not be answered and all
long scripture questions will not be
answered for time sake but we may be
able to point you in the direction of a
DVD or CD that you can purchase by
calling office so please be as direct as
possible with your questions so we can
be as direct as possible with our
answers out of the King James Bible no
other Bibles will be acknowledged on
this program also keep in mind that this
is a live stream and you May begin to
send in your questions at this time even
questions that pertain to everlasting
life we're just asking that you keep
your questions to a two scripture
maximum but let me introduce to you the
family that's on the panel this evening
at brother Dre good
evening brother Julius good evening
everybody brother Jerome Jon peace
brother James good evening everyone
sister Deborah
good evening brother Sean good evening
and we have the guest caller with us and
I'm brother Cornell sister Deborah let
us begin with our first question of the
evening uh yes there are several held
over questions that will be answered
first before getting into tonight's Q&A
so brother Israel as in Genesis 7: 1 2
and 3 at 3
it looks like God has giv us foul of the
air for food is this before Leviticus 11
was
given yeah definitely before yeah
Genesis came first Genesis 71 and3 that
was before Leviticus let's go and read
that uh brother James let's go to that
Genesis 7 and pick it up at verse one
because they said that verse three looks
like God has giv us fouls of the air for
food but he is not in this verse read it
brother and the Lord said unto Noah Come
Thou and all thy house into the ark for
the for thee have I seen righteous
before me in this generation of every
clean Beast Thou shalt take to thee by
sevens the male and his female and
beasts that are not clean by two the
male and his female of fouls also of the
air by sevens the male and the female to
keep seed alive upon the face of all the
Earth so you see what the Lord saying
that three of files also of the air by
sevens the male and the female that you
may keep the seed aive so these are
things that may be eaten when you see
them seven by seven but everything that
was not then you just brought them in by
two but if you read down further you see
that the Lord was getting ready to
destroy the face of the Earth read verse
four brother go ahead or yet seven days
and I will cause it to rain upon the
Earth 40 days and 40 nights and every
living substance that I have made will I
destroy from off the face of the Earth
so at this time when we read that
Genesis 7 meat was not even on the table
for man so he was not eating anything at
that time pertaining to meat he was a
vegetarian or fruit caring but let's see
when me did come on the picture let's go
into Genesis the 9th chapter Genesis
9 and let's pick it up at that verse one
and this is where you're seeing meat
being put on the table but not in
Genesis 7 and 1 through3 go ahead
brother and God blessed Noah and his
sons and said unto them be fruitful and
multiply and replenish the Earth m mhm
and the fear of you and the dread of you
shall be upon every beast of the earth
and upon every foul of the air upon all
that moveth upon the Earth and upon all
the fishes of the sea into your hand are
they
delivered yes every moving thing that
liveth shall be meat for you even as the
green herb have I given you all things
so when it said here that every moving
thing that liveth shall be meat for you
that's everything that's according to
God's dietary law the things that he say
that you shall eat and the things that
you shall not
eat let's go on Leviticus 11 right quick
Leviticus
11 and let's get straight down to read
that verse uh 46 because we just want it
understood that there's things that you
can eat and cannot eat pick it up at
that verse 46 what the Lord say this is
the law of the Beast and of the foul and
of every living creature that moveth in
the waters and of every creature that
creepeth upon the Earth to make a
difference between the unclean and the
clean and between the Beast that may be
eaten and the Beast that may not be
eaten so the Lord is letting it be known
here that there is a dietary law last
place Deuteronomy 14 let's go there
Deuteronomy 14
okay let's just bag that up what the
Lord said about the things that shall be
eaten and shall not be eaten Deuteronomy
14 pick it up read 11 and 12 for
me Deuteronomy 14: 11 and 12 of all
clean Birds ye shall eat but these are
they of which ye shall not eat the eagle
and the oaas and the Osprey and the oh
and the osprey
that was 11 and 12 okay so skip down to
verse 20 that' be the last verse go
ahead but of all clean fouls you may eat
so you can eat of everything that the
Lord say you can eat that's considered
clean fouls and the things that are
unclean you cannot eat but Leviticus
came after Genesis and the Lord was not
giv him permission to eat that in
Genesis 7 verses 1 through3 that's all I
get and we hope that ansed your question
question as we move on to our next
question yes moving on J uh Josephine
Smith says according to Deuteronomy 23
verse two can you please explain it for
me all right why don't we go to
Deuteronomy
23 when you get there James read that
verse two and the guest caller will take
it from there Deuteronomy 23 and: 2 a
bastard shall not enter into the
congregation
of the Lord even to his 10th Generation
shall he not enter into the congregation
of the
Lord no I cannot answer
that all I have to say all right so
we're going to keep it moving to our
next question keeping it moving the
where as is the use of the word
Christianity wrong when referring to our
religion if you are under the doctrine
of iog example if someone asks what
religion are you we should answer I am a
Christian
right share some light on that
question no it's not wrong for you to
refer to yourself as a Christian when
when you referring to your faith in
Jesus Christ and his true Doctrine the
doctrine which the Israelite God do
teach okay let's go to acts the 11th
chapter acts the 11th
chapter and brother James can you pick
it up at 19 and we're gonna
skip okay acts 11 and 19 now they which
were scattered abroad upon the
persecution that arose about Stefan
traveled as far as pH and cyphus and
Antioch preaching the word to none but
unto the Jews only now now take note in
that 19th verse it read about the uh
Jews only right it mentioned about the
Jews only the Jews in Antioch and a few
other places but we going to focus on
Antioch skip down to verse 25 read to
the
26 okay then departed Barnabas to Tarsus
for to seek Saul and when he had found
him he brought him un Antioch and it
came to pass that a whole year they
assembled themselves with the church and
taught much people and the disciples
were called Christians first in Antioch
so the Israelite Jews that follow Christ
they were call Christians first in
Antioch and these Israelite
Jews you okay they are the original
Christians
okay and as quiet as it kept these
Israelite Jews are
our ancestors we are day descendants to
so-called
negro that's all I got on it matter of
fact can you can you read one more place
I'm sorry can you read first Peter go to
First Peter the 4th chapter and read
just one verse verse 16 and that'll be
it 1 Peter 4
and6 yeah yet if any man suffer as a
Christian let him not be ashamed but let
him glory god on this behalf okay that
that's all I got
on all right nothing wrong with being
called a Christian what's up all right
be no ROM Christian though yeah
yeah all right hope that ansed your
question as we move on to our next
moving on Doc Martin asks if Jesus is
going to to start his Judgment at the
church is this church the Israelites
only or all believers or followers of
Christ all my family are Sunday church
goers and don't want to hear what I am
trying to tell them about being
Israelites all right brother Julius what
about that let's see what the book said
let's go to uh that first Peter the 4th
chapter yes is going to start at his
church and and is is true church because
the true church like Jerome just said uh
the the True Church of God started in
the wilderness under the hand of
Moses and graduated all the way down to
the
apostles so the Sunday church is another
Jesus another gospel let's go to First
Peter 4 and brother Jam please read
verse 16 and 17 1 Peter 4
16 and 17 yes J is going to start in the
house of the Lord what the book say yet
if any man suffer as a Christian let him
not be ashamed but let him glorify God
on this behalf a Christian is a one who
follows the teachings and writings of
Jesus Christ and spreads them continue
at 17 for the time has come that
judgment must begin at the house of God
and if it began at us what shall the end
be of them that obey not the gospel of
God how could they hear about the gospel
of God when they've been given another
Jesus they got the right name but the
wrong Doctrine so now and this is why
they can't accept what you're saying
brother so let's let's let's go to acts
the 11th
chapter acts the 11th chapter brother
James
okay acts 11 acts 11 and we going to
read one
verse like brother Jerome just said the
true Christian the true followers of
Christ were the original followers of
Christ were Hebrew
Israelites Hebrew Israelites but
continue acts 11 and just give me verse
26 and I got one place after
this and when he had found him he
brought him unto Antioch and it came to
pass that a whole year they had
assembled themselves with the church and
taught much people and the disciples
were called Christians first in Antioch
so Jesus disciple every last one of them
was Hebrew Israelites so therefore they
are the original Christians and we are
their descendants so let's go to my last
place let's go to Second Corinthians the
11 chapter and let's look at what why
your people cannot understand what
you're teaching them or what you're
trying to bring to them second
Corinthians the 11th chapter okay and
pick it up we go on verse 2 to 4
we all have been given us being captives
we've all been given another Jesus until
the Lord opened up our understanding and
led us to a place where the true word of
God was being taught 2 Corinthians 11 we
going 2 to 4 go ahead brother for I am
jealous over you with Godly jealousy for
I have espoused you to one husband that
I may present you as a Chase virgin to
Christ Paul he Paul introduce you to the
true gospel and the true Jesus go ahead
why did he say it like that go ahead but
I fear least by any means as the serpent
beg galed Eve through her through his
subtility so your mind so your mind
should be corrupted from the Simplicity
that is in Christ continue for if he
that cometh preacheth another Jesus whom
we have not preached or if ye receive
another Spirit which she have not
received or another gospel which she
have not accepted you might bear May
might well bear with him that mean you
got to contend to you got to contend
with him you got to challenge him
because we've been giving another Jesus
the Jesus of the Bible keeps the S uh
set up the Sabbath day which is the
seventh day the Jesus the of the world
gave you the first day Sunday that's why
they go to church on Sunday the Jesus of
the Bible tell you that when when you
die you go to the grave but that other
Jesus teaches that you go to heaven
the Jesus of the uh Bible says nobody
gets salvation or will be saved until
until he come back first resurrection
the Jesus uh the other Jesus of the
world teaches that uh anytime you
confess you saved already uhuh so that's
why they can't receive what you're
saying
brother so Jud is going to start in the
True Church of God the True Church of
God because he got to start in his
church and then from there on out
throughout the world
that's all I got Corel anybody want to
answer
that all right thank you for that
brother hope that answer their question
as we move on to our next one moving on
what about the Ethiopian Bible the
oldest Bible before King James and the
rest should we follow those original
scripts all right I don't know where
they get the proof of it being the
oldest Bible but the King James Bible is
the only Bible that we acknowledge on
this program and that we obey but uh
brother Julius got a little Lighty like
the shed on that go right ah here
brother this term Ethiopian Bible keeps
coming up first of all the Ethiopian
Bible is not the oldest Bible in the
world it is the Hebrew Bible the lord
gave his Commandments to Israel he told
you in the Psalms he never gave his word
to nobody else but Israel he never gave
his word to Ethiopia which are hites he
gave it to them that they can learn how
to learn salvation but Jesus told you
that salvation is of the Jews then so
what the Ethiopian Bible is a
translation of the Greek septu the septu
the Greek version of the Bible it is a
translation Ethiopian Bible is split up
into three sections and it came abroad
around the fourth to the sixth
Century they say it's some 800 years
older than the King James but the King
James is a translation but it has proven
to be the most accurate but the
Ethiopian Bible got 88 books in it
including them Lost Books including the
Lost Books of the Apocrypha which is not
uh ordained or ratified by the god of
Israel so this Ethiopian Bible subject
matter keeps coming up it is not the
oldest H uh trans translation it's a
translation based off of the Roman
Christian septu which with the which
they got from the Greeks so therefore it
is not the oldest it is not accurate it
is not accurate it's got some it
contains the books of the Bible but it
contains 88 well like brother Corell
said the kjb that we use contains 66 and
and all those 66 book appertain to
salvation but them other books the books
do not that's all I got brother
Cornel all right thank you for that
brother some good light shared there
hope that answer that question next
question next question Malik Shakur asks
what does Psalms 30 verse5 mean and
Psalms
37:1 who are the meek all right brother
Dre what you say as you share some light
on these two scriptures here let's go to
Psalm 30 and we're going to read verse
five the meek are those that in that are
going to inhabit the Earth is what Jesus
said in in
Matthew uh he said the meek shall un
have the Earth in Matthew
55 but Psalm 30 read verse five brother
go ahead for is anger endureth but a
moment in his favor is life weeping may
endure for a night but joy cometh in the
morning that's right that's right joy
cometh in the morning weeping may endure
for a night let's go to Psalms 103 and
look at this look at look at let's let's
see what else it says about that
okay Psalms 103 verse eight brother go
ahead the Lord is merciful and gracious
slow to anger and penth in Mercy mhm he
will not always chide neither will he
keep his anger forever
that's right so the Lord will not always
be angry and he won't keep his anger
forever go ahead he will not I'm sorry
he have not dwelt with us after our sins
nor rewarded us according to our
iniquities that's right skip down to
verse
17 but the mercy of the Lord is from
Everlasting to Everlasting upon them
that fear him and his righteousness unto
children's children
this is where his Mercy is his Mercy is
on them that fear him and his
righteousness unto their children's
children Verse 18 go ahead to such as
keep his Covenant and to those that
remember his Commandments to do them
that is who his Mercy is with he is
merciful to those now let's go to Psalm
126 and we just going read verse five
there Psalms 126 and verse
5 they that so in tears shall reap in
Joy that's right so you may sew in some
tears right now but if you endure and
you walking in this
word without hesitation you will reap in
joy in season so just be patient about
that now the other passage of scripture
was
Psalm
37 Psalm it was yeah Psalm
37 verse 11 who are the meek let's go
there Psalm 37 verse
11 when you get it go ahead brother but
the meek shall inherit the earth and
shall Delight themselves in the
abundance of Peace that's right because
that's where the peace is going to come
from from the Lord and that's the same
thing that Jesus said in Matthew 5
and5 now let's go to one other place
let's go to Psalm
25 verses 9 and
10 Psalm 25 verses 9 and 10 the meek
will he guide in judgment and the meek
will he teach his way all the paths of
the Lord are mercy and Truth unto such
as keep his Covenant and his tou
testimonies that's who the meek the meek
are those that are humbl those that
humble themselves to the Lord the meek
are those that submit to God and he
shows Mercy to them that keep his
testimonies I hope that
helps sir thank you for that brother
it's a beautiful thing to be
me yes sir all right we're g to move on
to our next question moving on be alert
as for you to please show where in the
scripture Jesus will return on the day
of atonement when the scriptures will
Jesus return on the day of atonement
guess caller can you share some
light yes let's start it with the coming
of Jesus in 1 Thessalonians the 4th
chapter and we're going to read one
verse verse
16 1 Thessalonians 4 and verse
16 for the Lord himself shall descend
from heaven with a shout with the voice
of the arch angel and with the Trump of
God and the dead in Christ shall rise
first now we read a little
more then we which are alive and remain
shall be caught up together with them in
the clouds to meet the Lord in the air
and so shall we ever be with the Lord
and that's when Jesus come the dead
going to be raised and the uh uh uh
living going to be change they going to
meet the Lord in air at the sound of
arel at the voice of arkangel of the
sound of a trumpet now let's go and see
what trumpet that is let's go into 1
Corinthians
15 chapter and we're going to read
verses 15 and
52 1 Corinthians 15 and vers uh 15-
52 now
this verses 50- 52 50 through
52 now this I say Brethren the that
flesh and blood cannot inherit the king
kingdom of God neither doeth corruption
inherit
incorruption behold I show you a mystery
we shall not all sleep but we shall all
be changed in a moment in the twinkling
of of an eye at the last Trump for the
trumpet shall sound and the dead shall
be raised Incorruptible and we shall be
changed so now that's talking about at
the same time the first Thessalonians
the 4th chapter the when Jesus
descend the seven trumpet the last Trump
which is the seven trumpet is going to
be blown then the dead going to be
raised that only going to happen on the
seven trumpet at the coming of Jesus now
let's go the 25th chapter and read verse
9 that was the 25th chapter of what what
book
sir Leviticus 25 Leviticus
25 verse
n 25 and verse Leviticus 25 and verse 9
says then shalt thou cause the trumpet
of the jubil to sound on the 10th day of
the seventh month in the day of
atonement shall you make the trumpet
sound throughout all your
land that trumpet of Jubilee is the
seventh trumpet and that seventh trumpet
going to be blown that's when Jesus
going to start his descent that's when
Jesus going to come down that's when the
dead going to be raised and the living
going to be changed and that seven
trumpets also called the the trumpet of
Jubilee and it's going to be sound on
the day of atonement
okay all I have to say all right hope
that answered your question there sister
Deborah time check the time is
7:59 byan Israel asked in Deuteronomy 22
verse1 and Leviticus 19 verse 19 why are
we not supposed Dom Mingo lenen and
W all right Deuteronomy 22 and11 let's
there and in Leviticus 19:19 why are we
not supposed to mingle linen with wool
and the guest caller would take it from
there go
read
22 Deuteronomy 22 And1 says Thou shalt
not wear a garment of diverse sorts as
of Woolen and linen together
now let's go into Leviticus
19-9 Leviticus 19-9 says ye shall keep
my statutes Thou shalt not let thy
cattle gender with a diverse kind Thou
shalt not sow thy filled with mingled
seed neither shall a garment mingle of
linen and Woolen come upon
thee okay we should not do it because
God said don't do it other than that I
don't know
all I have to
say all right hope that answers your
question as we move on to our
next next question uh Brother Jay
said when Jesus was Man In the Flesh and
he have and he have to have
faith in the father okay when Jesus was
Man In the Flesh did he have to have
faith in the father to perform his
miracles brother Julius what you say
absolutely
absolutely let's go and look at way he
got this Faith from let's go to St John
the thir chapter brother James okay St
John the thir
chapter and pick it up and read verse 6
for God so loved the world that he gave
his only begotten son that whosoever
believeth in him should not perish but
have everlasting life now Faith is the
your belief the evidence of things hope
uh the uh the things the evidence of
things the evidence of things hope for
the evidence of things not seen your
faith is your belief so the father gave
his son to whosoever believe on him why
believe on him him continue all the way
down to verse 35 and we'll move for God
sent not his son into the world to
condemn the world read verse 35 oh verse
35 okay yes the Father loveth the Son
and have given all things into his hand
so if he gave all things into his hand
what must we have what was he full of
because he had to teach us let's go to
Hebrews the 12th chapter and get this
answer Hebrews 12 we going to read
verses one and
two because you can't get no greater
witness than our Lord and Savior Jesus
the
Christ when you get it brother verse one
Hebrews 12 And1 go ahead wherefore
seeing we also are compassed about with
so great a cloud of witnesses let us lay
aside every weight and the sin which
doth so easily beset us and let us run
with patience the race that is set
before us and Jesus ran his race like so
we got to run our race continue at verse
two why what who is Jesus and what is he
what is he full of go ahead looking unto
Jesus the author and finisher of our
faith that's good enough right there
Jesus is the author and the finisher of
our faith he's the beginning of our
faith and he's the end of our faith
that's why he said that if uh he that
believeth on me hey the same shall be
saved you even and you got to endure
until the end you got to believe until
the end and how do you do that if you
love him you going to keep his
Commandments that's all I got brother
Cornel that's
right yes
call I want to throw in a couple of
things go to Hebrews the 10th chapter
the question was that Jesus have
faith Hebrews Hebrews the 10th chapter
and start reading at verse 10 thank
you Hebrews 10 verse1
by the which will we are Sanctified
through the offering of the body of
Jesus Christ once and for
all go ahead and every priest standeth
daily ministering and offering often
times the same sacrifices which can
never take away
sins but this man but this man after he
had offered one sacrifice for sins
forever set down on the right hand of
God
go ahead from hence from hence forth
expecting till his enemies be made his
foot stool for for
by after Jesus
came and he died and rose again you know
he said that he now he
expecting to
be the enemies to be his foot stol he's
expecting that
why did he expect that because he
believed what God told him let me go and
show you what God told him let's go to
Psalms 110 and
one
okay Psalms Psalm 110
one okay the Lord said unto my Lord sit
thou at my right hand until I make thine
enemies thy foot
stol so now that was said to him
uh uh in the days of David because David
wrote that so when he came and died for
the
sin he said and he was and uh rose again
he was expecting his uh uh uh uh uh
enemies he was
expected to be uh his enemies to become
his foot stol and the reason he expected
that because God told him that in10
chapter P so that mean he believed the
word of
God so he had faith in the word of the
father that's all I have to say he did
yes sir thank
you all right yep like it was said the
father gave him the spirit without
measure without
measure all right hope that answered
your question as we move on to our next
one moving
on uh we can talk right here as is
there is is it a sin to shave your head
I heard someone use Leviticus 21 verse 5
can you explain and MC asks are there
any scriptures for cutting our
hair all right sound like a two-part
question there is it a sin to shave your
head what you say brother
Jerome well the verse that you're
actually referring to has to do with the
uh sons of Aaron all right now the
congregation of Israel that's something
all together different okay so now let's
go to
um Leviticus the 21st
chapter okay I'm there and we gonna read
verse one and Skip and read verse 5 and
6 Leviticus 21 verse1 and the Lord said
unto Moses speak unto the priests the
sons of Aaron and say unto them there
shall none be defiled for the dead among
his people five and six they shall not
make baldness upon their head neither
shall they shave off the corners of
their beard nor make any cuting in their
flesh they shall be holy unto their God
and not profane the name of their God
for the offerings of the Lord made by
fire and the bread of their God they do
offer therefore they shall be be holy
yeah so that's regarding the sons of
Aaron where he he said when they go to
make they uh offerings before me in the
temple in the house of God he say I
don't want them to make bald their heads
that's talking to um the sons of Aaron
now your second question was are there
any scriptures concerning cutting our
hair now that right MCS that one okay
let's go now let's go to Leviticus 19
for that one
okay and at 19 pick it up at 1 and two
and then we going to
skip and the Lord spake unto Moses
saying Speak unto all the congregation
of the children of Israel and say unto
them ye shall be holy for I the Lord
your God am Holy now we talking about
the whole congregation now right now
skip down to verse
27 verse 27 ye shall not round the
corners of your heads neither shalt thou
Mar the corners of thy beard yeah you
know that's all I got on anybody want to
ask something they can yeah I want to
throw something in okay I want to go
back to the first scripture we read
Leviticus what was it 21 that was 21
and5 sir yeah okay read it and listen to
what it say go ahead they they shall not
make baldness upon their head neither
shall they shave off the corner of their
beard nor make any cuting in their
flesh for
what they shall be holy unto their God
and not profane the name of their God
for the offerings of the Lord made by
fire and the bread of their God they do
offer therefore they shall be holy and
when you read it like that it sound like
they should not do that period but now
back back up to the first verse and see
what it
says and the Lord said unto Moses speak
unto the priest the sons of Aaron and
say unto them there shall none be
defiled for the dead among his
people so and that's the whole thing you
should not defile for the dead among his
people by what by shaving your head okay
and make and read a little more but for
his kin that is near unto him that is
for his mother and for his father and
for his son and for his daughter and for
his brother and for his sister of Virgin
that is nigh unto him which hath had no
husband for her may he be
defiled okay then but the whole thing
was started you don't shave your head
for because of which
conditions ver is for the dead that's
all I have to say and uh all right uh
also in that Leviticus 19 if you read
verse 28 it says the same thing for the
dead
that for the dead
yes okay I just want to make sure you
understand that it's not talking about
what you can't do you can do that uh but
you cannot do it for the Dead with any
kind of Mo de shave your head and
nothing else for the dead okay thank you
for
that all right hope that answered your
question is we keep on moving keeping it
moving barar still question is
responding to a question asked last week
which uh asked does the fourth
Commandment mean to mean no drawing
Angels or things in the sea like fish
can you explain so her question
is what if they draw what they think is
a picture of
Jesus what if they draw what they think
that's the key word think is a picture
of Jesus we got we got 10,000 different
religions out here and everybody draws a
picture of what they
think is God but let's go into that
Proverbs 3 let's go into Proverbs
3 because that that's something that you
shouldn't do it don't need to be done
and we're going to read some scriptures
to show that Proverbs
three Proverbs three one verse brother
we gonna read that verse five because
everybody is drawn according to
they Faith they religion what they think
God look like they got hundreds
thousands of different pictures out here
read three
and5 trust in the Lord with all thine
heart and lean not unto thine own
understanding that's why when you said
thinking there you're leaning to your
own understanding if you thinking that
you are drawing a picture of the Lord
here but let's go into Exodus the 20th
chapter we read it earlier Exodus the 20
chapter yes
sir and when you get there brother let's
pick it up at that verse
22 and
23 and let's see what it was that was
done
here Exodus 20: 22 and
23 and the Lord said unto Moses thus
Thou shalt say unto the children of
Israel
ye have seen that I have talked with you
from Heaven ye shall not make with me
gods of silver neither shall ye make
unto you gods of go all right skip up
and read three and four for
me thou shal have no other gods before
me thou shall not make unto thee any
Graven image or any likeness of anything
that is in heaven above or that is in
the in the earth beneath or that is in
the water under the Earth and we know
God is above so how can you draw a
picture no man has ever been there
before turn over to Deuteronomy
Deuteronomy the 4th chapter and let's
see when God came down to give the
Commandments what the people saw here
Deuteronomy the 4th
chapter and when you get there
brother pick it up at that verse 10
Deuteronomy 4 and10
especially the day that thou stood us
before the Lord thy God in Horeb when
the Lord said unto me gather me the
people together and I will make them
hear my words that they may learn to
fear me all the days they shall live
upon the Earth and that they may teach
their
children yes and ye came near and stood
under the mountain and the mountain
burned with fire un the midst of heaven
with dark Darkness clouds and thick
Darkness okay we talking about Darkness
clouds and thick Darkness go ahead and
the Lord spake unto you out of the midst
of the fire ye heard the voice of the
words but saw no similitude only ye
Heard a Voice so if you haven't saw any
similitude of what the Lord look like
but you only Heard a Voice what is it
that you
drawing verse 13 and he declared unto
you his Covenant which he commanded you
to perform even Ten Commandments and he
wrote them upon two tables of stone go
ahead and the Lord commanded me at that
time to teach you statutes and judgments
that you might do them in the land
whether ye go over to possess it uhhuh
two more verses take ye therefore good
heed unto yourselves for ye saw no
manner of similitude on the day that the
Lord spake un to you in horb out of the
midst of the fire you saw no no manner
of similitude of what the Lord looked
like because of the the thick clouds how
can you say that you drawing a picture
of him read that 16 least ye corrupt
yourselves and make you a Graven image
the similitude of any figure the
likeness of male or female so leave that
alone I mean you don't need to even
think that you drawing a picture of the
Lord because if they didn't see nothing
here thousands of years ago hasn't
Nobody seen nothing today and that's all
I
got all right hope that answered your
question let's move on to our next
moving on ik chuck woo Arman says as a
health care
professional how do we handle situations
on dietary needs for our patients
especially when pork and shrimp are
involved do we ask them to eat it or not
all right brother Julius we know you
know something about that what you say
bro as a former health care professional
I did my job when you say health care
professional there are many branches in
the Health Care system I don't know if
you didn't state in this question if you
were a dietitian or a medical dietitian
but I worked on the trade line and my
job was to put everything on that paper
that uh on as working on the trade line
put everything on the paper that The
dietitian suggested to the patients that
were admitted that's a dietician job do
they go and consult the patient and find
out what they eat that's their job so as
a professional I would suggest that you
do your job because now when you tell
them kind trying to control what people
eat uh you're going into a realm that
may not be pertinent to your job may or
may not be uh they ask the patients uh
do you eat pork or what kind of meat do
you like what do you don't dislike and
the dietician takes that information and
gives it to the trade line operator and
we take those trades to the patients so
because you can lose your job going
outside of your realm of employment
whatever your title is but you don't
force anything on nobody you don't force
your your faith or your religion on
anybody or what to eat that's their
choice unless they act you or something
like that and I've been in that
situation I did my job and I kept my job
because that was outside of my realm
that's what I suggest we can't tell
people what to eat or what not to eat so
that's the best I can do with that
Corell right thank you brother
appreciate that and let us MO move on to
our next
question next question ran 64 ask how
will the Saints be judged once they make
the first
resurrection or just the people in the
second Resurrection how will the Saints
be
judged brother Dre what you say let's go
to Revelation the 20th chapter and take
a look at this
Revelation and we going to pick it up at
verse vers 4 Revelation 20
and4 go ahead brother and I saw Thrones
and they set upon them and judgment was
given unto them and I saw the souls of
them that were beheaded for the witness
of Jesus and for the word of God and
which had not worshiped the Beast
neither his image neither had received
his Mark upon their foreheads or in
their hands and they lived and reigned
with Christ A Thousand Years I notice it
said I saw Thrones and they that sat
upon them and judgment was given onto
them they wasn't being judged I mean
they were the judges they were not being
judged judgment was given onto them
verse verse five go ahead brother but
the rest of the Dead Liv not again until
the thousand years were finished this is
the first resurrection so the people
that came up in the first resurrection
they were judges they were not being
judged go ahead blessed and holy is he
that have part in the First Resurrection
on such the second death have no power
but they shall be Priests of God and of
Christ and shall reign with him a
thousand years they don't so the second
death has no power on these they Rose in
the first resurrection so they don't
stand in judgment but they will be
judges so they won't be standing in
judgment these are those that come up in
the first
resurrection and for time sake you could
read about the rest of it on your own
those those that come up afterwards
after Satan is loose for after the
Thousand Years Satan is loose for a
minute read verse 10 go ahead brother
and the devil that deceived them was
cast into the lake of fire and brimstone
where the Beast and the false prophet
are and shall be tormented day and night
forever and ever now this is the second
one coming up go ahead and I saw a great
white throne and him that sat on it from
whose face the earth and the heaven fled
away and there was found no place for
them and I saw the dead small and great
stand before God and the books were open
and another book was open which is The
Book of Life and the dead were judged
out of those things which were written
in the books according to their Works go
ahead and the Sea gave up the dead which
were in it and death and Hell delivered
up the dead which were in them and they
were judged every man according to their
works these stood in judgment but those
that come up in the first resurrection
they don't stand in judgment they will
be judges go ahead that's that's all I
got
brother all right like you say brother
Dre everybody wise and hard is shooting
for their first resurrection yes sir all
right thank you for that brother hope
that answered their question sister
Deborah are we going into new territory
uh yes uh we are now into tonight's Q&A
for Wednesday November the 6 2020
24 Israel Lone Star says in Matthew 10
verse 28 explain please Matthew
10:28 because I know the Bible is the
soul okay that's so Randy Sams 36 there
yes all right Matthew 1028 Jerome share
some
light yeah let's go read that U brother
James
okay Matthews
10:28 and fear not them which kill the
body but are not able to kill the soul
but rather fear him which is able to
destroy both soul and Body in
hell yeah and as you said you know the
soul and the body is is one and the same
so let's go read Luke because Luke says
it as we really know it okay let's go to
Luke the 12th chapter and read verse 4
and
5 Luke 12: 4 and 5 says and I say unto
you my friends be not afraid of them
that kill the body and after that have
no more that they can do but I will
forewarn you whom ye shall fear fear Him
which after Heath killed ha power to
cast into hell yay I say unto you fear
Him yeah
so we know the soul as you said in the B
is one the same one more place go to
Leviticus the 5th chapter and read verse
1-5 okay
Leviticus it may be somebody out there
that haven't read these verses about the
soul and the body okay Leviticus 5
verses 1-5 yeah and if a soul sin and
hear the voice of swearing and is a
witness whether he has seen or known of
it if he do not utter it then he shall
bear his iniquity right so we talking
about the soul now we talking about a
soul that can hear go ahead or if a soul
touch any unclean thing whether it be a
carcass of an unclean Beast or a carcass
of an unclean cattle or the carcass of
an unclean creeping things and if it be
hidden from him he also shall be unclean
and guilty go ahead or if he touch the
unclean cleanness of a man whatsoever
uncleanness it be that a man shall be
defiled without thou and it be hid from
him when he knoweth of it then he shall
be guilty what
else characteristics does the soul have
read verse four or if a soul swear
pronouncing with his lips to do evil or
to do good whatsoever it be that a man
shall pronounce with an oath and it be
hid from him when he knoweth of it then
he shall be guilty in one of those
things verse five and it shall be when
things that he shall confess that he has
sinned in that thing yeah so all these
um characteristics we just read which
was referring to the soul are
characteristics of our body because the
soul and the body is one and the same
that's all I got on that's right I I we
throw one more in there
okay First Corinthians 15th chapter and
find the verse where it tell you the
first man Adam was
made first Corinthians
15 all right we are in search mode for
that
455 yes that is 45 do you want me to
start start at 44 and reading the
45 read it is sown a natural body it is
raised a spiritual body there is a
natural body and there is a spiritual
body and so it is written the first man
Adam was made a living Soul the last
Adam was made a quickening
spirit question is answer the first man
Adam was made a living Soul that's all I
have to say all right hope that answered
your question as we move on to our next
question moving on a Thomas asked in
Exodus 12 verse 23 was the death angel
and Holy Angel or a evil
angel let's go to Exodus 12 and
23 when you get there brother reading
and the guest caller would take it from
there was a death angel Holy Angel or an
evil
Exodus 12:23 says for the Lord will pass
through to Smite the Egyptians and when
he seeth the blood upon the lentil and
on the two side posts the Lord will pass
over the door and will not suffer the
Destroyer to come in unto your houses to
Smite
you it was an evil
angel go to
Psalms 78
read verses
43 through 44 and we going to skip down
Psalm
78: 43-
44 how he had wrought his signs in Egypt
and his wonders in the field of Z and
had turned their Rivers into blood and
their floods that they could not
drink skip down to 49 and read 49-
51 he cast upon them the fierceness of
his anger wrath and indignation and
Trouble by sending evil angels among
them he made a way to his anger he
spared not their soul from death but
gave their life over to pestilence and
smokee all the firstborn in Egypt the
chief of their strength in the
Tabernacles of
ham so the angels Death Angel was an
evil
angel all right hope that answered your
question there as we move
on moving on Kenn Kennedy Ray mckenny
says how do I explain to someone that we
will be God's only if you have done
right by God himself I've showed
scripture and they are still saying
that's not exactly saying we will be
Gods Julius share some light let's do
this let's uh let's do this
plan Genesis chapter 1 we gon to move
quick Genesis chapter 1 and verse
26 let's look at the plan of God for man
for his
creation Genesis 1 and
26 and God said let us make man in our
image after our likeness and let them
have dominion over the fish of the sea
and over the fowl of the air and over
the cattle and over the Earth and over
every creeping thing that creepeth upon
the Earth though man is created to rule
and
Reign your whole H life in this Flesh
and Blood body you are practicing to
overcome so you can rule and Reign but
you can start in this flesh let's move
on to Psalms the 82nd chapter Psalms 82
still Jesus talking Moses wrote about it
but now let's look at what the psalm is
what David had had what the Lord had
David write Psalm 82 and
one God standeth in the congregation of
the mighty he judgeth among the gods oh
showing you what man was created to be
and what man will
be skip down to verse
six I have said ye are gods and all of
you are children of the most high uhhuh
but ye shall die like men and fall like
one of the princes because man in the
beginning was not created to die but
because because Man was created to
become God but because man sin men die
so now let's go to St John the 10th
chapter and show you what he said he
told you I have said that ye are God I
have said that ye are Gods St John 10
read verse
34 and 35 go ahead
Jesus answered them it is not written in
your law read it again Jesus answered
them is it not written in your law I
said ye are Gods yeah he said it in
Psalms 82nd chapter go ahead if he
called them Gods unto whom the word of
God came and the scripture cannot be
broken because the scriptures can't be
broken why because imp it's impossible
for God to lie if he say you going to be
God
you are going to be god let's go to
First Corinthians the 15th chapter let's
see when when you become
God if you keep his Commandments and and
have faith until the end you going to be
what the Lord created you to be 1
Corinthians the 15
chapter and pick it up at verse
51 behold I show you a mystery we shall
not all sleep but we shall all be
changed in a moment and the twinkling of
an eye at the last
Trump told you earlier that that trumpet
that seven trumpet GNA sound that
announces the coming of the Lord and
that announces the uh the Dead Rising
being God and the righteous that are
living being changed to being God skip
down my brother to verse
53 for this corruptible must put on
incorruption and this Mor this Mortal
must put on immortality
go ahead so when this corruptible shall
have put on incorruption and this Mortal
shall have put on
immortality then shall be brought to
pass the saying that is written death is
swallowed up in Victory because death
was added to the creation because man
sin had man not sinned he would have
been what God wanted him to be at that
time but now my last place let's look
look look what Jesus said out of the
mouth of Jesus himself revelation second
chapter Revelation the 2 chapter
remember man in the beginning Genesis
let man have dominion over everything
Revelation 2 and 1 verse
26 and he that overcometh and keepeth my
Works unto the end to him will I give
power over the Nations hey you going to
be God you going to have all
power that's all I got I don't know what
else we could add to
that all right hope that answers your
question as we move on to our next one
with the time Check Yes moving on
8:36 the K family says is
self-gratification as Sin please provide
scriptures yes call it's it's self
gratification a
sin go to First John read three and four
the 3 chapter and verse
4 1 John 3 and verse 4 whosoever
committed sin transgresses also the law
for sin is the transgression of the
law that's all I have to say all right
hope that answered your question as we
move on to our next one moving on uh
kazia lee as is it unlawful for me to
prepare a seafood dish for my son even
though I don't eat it I told him I will
find out first if it was
okay well if you prep preparing a
seafood dish for your son you didn't
mention here whether it's clean or
unclean if it's unclean then it's not
right for you to prepare it for your
son let's go in Leviticus 11th
chapter even though you don't eat it hey
you still have to be sure
that you're not preparing it for
somebody else to eat if it's something
that the Lord say thou shalt not
eat Leviticus 11 when you get there
brother let's pick it up at that verse
nine Leviticus
119 these shall ye eat of all that are
in the waters whatsoever hath fins and
scales in the waters in the seas and in
the rivers then shall ye eat so if you
preparing a dish for your son and it
have fins and scales got to have them
both not one and not the other got to
have them both then it's cool for you to
prepare for your son keep reading and
are and all that have not fins and
scales in the seas and in the rivers of
all that move in the waters and of any
living thing which is in the waters they
shall be an Abomination unto you
be giving your son an Abomination to eat
verse 11 they shall be even an
Abomination unto you ye shall not eat of
their flesh but ye shall have but ye
shall have their carcasses in
Abomination whatsoever have no fins nor
scales in the waters that shall be an
Abomination unto you so if you preparing
it and if it don't have those fins and
and those scales and no you should not
be preparing it for your challenge skip
down and read verse
45 and um 46 go ahead for I am the Lord
that bringeth you up out of the land of
Egypt to be your God ye shall therefore
be holy for I am
Holy this is the law of the Beast and of
the foul and of every living creature
that moveth in the waters and of every
creature that creepeth upon the Earth
one more verse to make a difference
between the unclean and the clean and
between the Beast that may be eaten and
the Beast that may not be eaten so if
you're preparing for your child some
seafood dish hey it has to be the animal
that can be eaten that is the key word
now go quickly to Proverbs 22 and read
verse for me Proverbs
22 and read verse 6 for
me Proverbs
22 and verse six
says train up a child in the way he
should go and when he is old he will not
depart from it so he didn't mention age
either here but you're supposed to train
up a child because it doesn't matter
even if it's your son and he grown and
he don't know no better you should let
him know that the dishes that you can
prepare him are the things that shall be
eaten and not the things that shall not
be eaten and then he should be able to
turn around and teach it to his children
and to their children's children that's
how you keep God's program going that's
all I got on
that and we hope that that answers your
question next question next question
Solomon uh truth TV said as for
Tabernacles weekly offering would ties
represent the burnt offerings Julius
what you say I had to look at this
question real good but Tabernacle weekly
offering let's go to Leviticus with t no
ties is a commandment of God that's the
10th of your
first let's go to Leviticus the 23rd
chapter and remember this is the levitic
the 23rd chapter uh all these burnt
offerings and sacrifice that was done
under levitical priesthood which is no
longer in
force Leviticus 23 read verses 33 and
34 and the Lord spake unto Moses saying
Speak unto the children of Israel saying
the 15th day of this seventh month shall
be the Feast of Tabernacles for seven
days unto the Lord so now the Feast of
Tabernacles is seven days okay it's
seven days so now but you read further
down it gets all into sacrifices and
stuff are made by fire we don't do that
no more Jesus came and took and took
care of all that by sacrificing himself
so how do we sacrifice uh
today especially us being in captivity
let's go to Hebrews the 13th
chapter Hebrews the 13th chapter Jesus
said if you love me keep my Commandments
and then when you do that Hebrews 13 and
pick it up at verse
12 wherefore Jesus also that he might
sanctify the people with his own blood
suffered without the gate because he was
a sin offering so by his stripes we are
he continue let us go forth therefore
unto him without the camp bearing his
reproach go ahead
for here we have no continuing City but
we seek one to come yes by him therefore
let us offer the sacrifice of praise to
God continually that is the fruit of our
lips giving thanks to his name so now
that is the way we serve the Lord and
that is the way we please him you keep
his Commandments and you be thankful to
him for all things giving him thanks for
all things no more burnt offerings none
of that but your tithe you still do
because it is a
commandment so what he want that he want
your tip of your
income that's all I
got thank you just go and read where it
said three times a
year should come before me let's see
what it says there that's Deuteronomy 16
and verse 16 Deuteronomy 16 verse1 16
says three times in a year shall all
males appear before the Lord thy God in
the place which he shall choose in the
Feast of unleavened bread and in the
Feast of Weeks and in the Feast of
Tabernacles and they shall not appear
before the Lord
empty read the next verse every man
shall give as he is able according to
the blessing of the Lord thy God which
he hath given
thee that's talking about
money even though you do your an you did
your animal sacrifice then you still had
to tithe with money so the animal
sacrifice uh igus don't represent animal
sacrifice animal sacrifice represent
animal
sacrifice but the tithe was there all
the time along with your animal
sacrifice that is right and that was
that's all I have to say all right thank
you hope that aned your question
question we continue to move on to our
next continuing to move on a Thomas
asked for explanation for Joe 41 what is
a
leviathan was it here before
Noah and
the go
ahead was it here before nor in the
flood and if so is it here
today all right let go to job
41 okay read that verse one let's open
it up to the
panel can thou draw out Leviathan with a
hook or his tongue with a cord which
thou letest
down open to the
pen well for
me I don't have a clue what that
is okay so we'll um we'll leave it right
there in our next question
yes Malicia cure
as when the death and blind make it into
the kingdom will they receive their
sight and
hearing brother Dre what you say let's
go to uh Psalms 103 Psalms
103 and uh we're gonna pick it up at
verse
two Psalm 103 and2 says bless the Lord
oh my soul and forget not all his
benefits right go ahead who forgiveth
all thy iniquities who Health all thy
diseases H it didn't say some of thy
diseases it says who heals all thy
diseases go ahead who redeemeth thy life
from destruction who crowneth thee with
loving kindness and Tender Mercies who
redeems thy life from d destruction who
crowneth thee with Tender Mercies let's
go to uh 1 Corinthians 15 1 Corinthians
15 and we're gonna pick it up at verse
35 1 Corinthians 15 and
35 but some man will say how are the
dead raised up and with what body do
they come what kind of body are they
gonna come with go ahead th fool that
which thou seest is not quickened except
it
die and that which thou sest thou sest
not the body that shall be but bear
grain it may CH it may chance of wheat
or some other grain so the body that is
sown is not the body that shall be but
that body Bears grain skip down to verse
there are also celestial bodies and
bodies terrestrial but the glory of the
celestial is one and the glory of the
terrestrial is another so they are
heavenly bodies and they are Earthly
bodies and their Glory differs one from
another skip down to verse
42 so also is the resurrection of the
dead it is sown in in corruption it is
raised in incorruption so it is sown in
corruption we have a body that's
corruptible because after Adam sin this
old body started
dying go ahead it is sown in dishonor it
is raised in glory it is sown in
weakness it is raised in
power it is sown a natural body it is
raised a spiritual body there's an is
raised a spiritual body it is sewn in
the ground a natural body it is raised a
spiritual
body and I ain't seen I heard I read
about no spiritual body that's
blind no
sir neither death brother who Health all
of thy diseases and sicknesses so I'm
sure he
will okay I got one other place let's go
to uh Revelation 21 read verses four and
five Revelation
[Music]
21 verses four and five
says and God shall wipe away all tears
from their eyes and there shall be no
more death neither sorrow nor crying
neither shall there be any more pain for
the former things are passed
away and he and he that sat upon the
throne said behold I make all things new
and he said unto me right for these
words are true and faithful I make all
things new this body Bears grain it's
not going to be the natural body so if
you blind you g to have a spiritual body
okay and the Lord is going to raise you
and you won't be
corruptible so that's that's the answer
for
that that is correct brother thank you
for that hope that answer that question
next question next question natural
candy girl asks can we celebrate
Thanksgiving yes caller coming up soon
it's Thanksgiving what you say
there's nothing in uh there's nothing
written in the Bible that say that
speaks against it or said you
cannot so I can't make no comment on it
all right and we GNA keep it moving with
the time check yes the time is 8:50 TX
Domino uh ask for you to explain Genesis
3: 14 and 15 in verse 14 where it reads
cursed are you above all livestock and
all wild
animals 15 concerning the crushing head
and striking the heel want
expanation all right so let's go to that
Genesis
3 Genesis 3 when you get there brother
James read 14 and
15 and um let's get a light shed on that
one by the guas
call okay Genesis 3: 14- 15 says and the
Lord God said unto the serpent because
thou has done this Thou Art cursed above
all cattle and above every beast of the
field upon thy belly shalt thou go and
dust shalt thou eat all the days of thy
life and I will put enity between thee
and the woman and between thy seed and
her seed and it shall bruise brise thy
head and thou shal bruise his
heel first thing is let's see uh you
know what who this what this serpent is
is you know let's go in the 12th chapter
of Revelation read verse
9 Revelation
12 and verse n
says and the Great Dragon was cast out
that old serpent called the devil and
Satan which deceiveth the whole world he
was cast out into the Earth and his
angels were cast out with him so now
that serpent in the garden was satting
the devil because the serpant is nothing
but another one of his names he was not
a literal snake so he was not cast to
the ground like a snake that crawled on
the ground the only thing I can see that
the Lord did was take the power away
from him to pop up in front of
somebody let's look go and you uh uh go
to uh uh go to Jude and read the six
verse in Jude 6
okay Jude
six little book before
Revelation and the angels which kept not
their first estate but left their own
habitation he had reserved an
everlasting ing chains under Darkness
until the Judgment of the great
day now Satan was the chief of the
Angels left the first estate just like
he popped up in front of Eve and uh uh
and talked with her God took that power
away from him just took some of his
power away and then it said going to be
a uh going to be you know war between uh
uh the woman's seed and Satan seed well
let's see who the woman SE is let's go
back to 12 back up 12th chapter and
verse one from 1 to
5 okay Revelation 12 veres 1-5 says and
there appeared a great Wonder in heaven
a woman clothed with the Son and the
moon under her feet and upon her head a
crown of 12 stars and she being with
child cried travailing in birth and
paying to be delivered and there
appeared another Wonder in heaven and
Behold a great red dragon having seven
heads and 10 horns and seven crowns upon
his heads and his tail drew the third
part of the stars of heaven and did cast
them to the earth and the dragon stood
before the woman which was ready to be
delivered for to devour her child as
soon as it was born and she brought
forth a Manchild who was to rule all
nations with a rod of iron and her child
was caught up unto God and to his
throne so now that's the that's the
woman seed that he's talking about this
man child is Jesus who is going to be
and so now and and it said also that he
was cursed Beyond any other Beast why
was he cursed Beyond any other Beast
because the Beast just died let's see
what's going to happen to the serpent go
to Revelation 20th chapter
and read verse
10 Revelation 20 and verse 10 and the
devil that deceived them was cast into
the lake of fire and brimstone where the
Beast and the FR false prophet are and
shall be tormented day and night forever
and ever and that's not going to happen
to any beast that's going to happen to
angels and Men that's all I have to say
all right hope that answered your
question as we can continue to move on
and Deborah we going to definitely try
and get these last two questions in go
right ahead oh all right
um Andrew uh wants you to
explain Exodus 25 verse
13 Exodus 25 and
13 uh Jeron what you say let's go take a
look at it
okay you get it go ahead and read and
thou shalt make staves of shamwood and
overlay them with
gold and those things are are are are
long poles that you that you put in the
uh Arc of the that's put in the Arc of
the Covenant you know and this was
happening during the time of the uh the
old Covenant um when they had the Ark of
the Covenant
um um let's read verse um 10 through
15 verse 10 through 15 and they shall
make an arc of shamwood two cubits and a
half shall be the length thereof and a
cubit and a half the bread thereof and a
cubit and a half the height thereof and
thou shalt overlay it with pure gold
within and without shalt thou overlay it
and shall make upon it a crown of gold
round about and thou shalt cast four
rings of gold for it and put them in the
four corners thereof and two rings shall
be in the one side of it and two rings
in the other side of
ites inside throughout the Rings and
that's attached to the Arc of the
Covenant so that they can carry and not
touch the arc at all they carrying it by
the staves go ahead and thou shalt make
staves of shamwood
and overlay them with gold and thou
shalt put the staves into the Rings by
the sides of the ark that the ark may be
born with
them the stav shall be in the rings of
the Ark they shall not be taken from it
that that's all I got
him that's right you're WR them stage
play an important part they messed up
and didn't do it according that and the
man lost his life yeah all right we go
keep it moving to our looks like our
final question
Deborah all right uh Sanders Herring
says uh in Romans 16 Verse 22 I
turus who wrote this epistle salute you
in the Lord didn't Paul write Romans and
secondly SE uh Zephaniah 1 verse 5 who
is
malum okay first part Romans 16
in verse
22 they want to know about who wrote
this and the guest caller will share
some light from
there
sure this guy uh uh uh why don't you go
this guy go and read 622 And1 real
quick six uh Romans 16 and 22 or
21 22 okay I T torist who wrote this
epistle salute you in the
Lord that's obvious that this guy was a
scribe most of the Apostles and the
prophets didn't do no right in
themselves they had
scribes but some but uh something
happened a few times and Paul had to
write it with his own hand let's go
into verse
19 Fon verse
and okay let me get to it sorry about
that yeah First Timothy second Timothy
Titus and
then okay I'm almost
there okay and filon which which
scripture again
sir verse 19 says I Paul have written it
with my own hand I will repay it all bet
allbe it I do not say to thee how thou
OST owest unto me even thy own self
besides see now something there he said
he had to write with his own
hand let's go to fir uh uh 2
Thessalonians 3 And1
17 second
Thessalonians
3 2 Thessalonians 3 and
says the salutation of Paul with mine
own hand which is the token in every
epistle so I
write okay so that when he whatever that
was he wrote with his own hand now
Galatians 6 and verse
11 Galatians
6 and verse 11
says ye see how large a letter I have
written unto you with mine own
hand see because all the apostles and
the prophets you know these people
didn't do a lot of right they had
scribes that's why when uh uh you look
at the Bible it's talk about scribes and
Pharisees what is a scribe he's one that
do all the writing for all the
people this guy did the writing but the
words he wrote was the words that Paul
gave him therefore Paul is the one that
uh uh uh that put forth these uh uh
Romans and all the other scriptures that
he wrote okay now the last one Z zani
one and five yes sir
read and them that worship the host of
Heaven upon the housetops and them that
worship and that swear by the Lord and
that swear by malol
okay want to know who is malol let's go
quickly because this malol is nothing
but an alanite
idol let's go to First Kings
11:5 First Kings 11 and5
says for Solomon went after ashth the
goddess of the South zidonians and after
Malcolm the Abomination of the
ammonites it was an ammonite Idol it
spelled a little different but that's
what malol is it's ain't nothing but an
ammonite Pagan God an idol that they
worship that's all I have to say all
right and we hope that that aned your
question as we end our program on that
question there sister Deborah time chck
uh the time is
9:03 all right we like to thank
everybody from all around the world who
tuned in with us and asked those great
questions we took joy and answering them
for you and if you submitted a question
and we did not have the chance to get to
it please don't resubmit your question
sister Deborah take it put it in
rotation and we will answer your
question next week so until we all come
together again please be safe out there
be blessed and may the Lord have mercy
on us all as brother James closes us out
Our Father which art in heaven Hallowed
be thy name thy kingdom come thy will be
done in earth as it is in heaven give us
this day our daily bread and forgive us
our debts as we forgive our debt TOs and
lead us not into temptation but Deliver
Us from Evil for thine is the kingdom
and the power and the glory forever in
Jesus name we pray amen